(403) 481-1522

Full Stack Developer Github

jayden.shaw@gmail.com LinkedIn

# **Summary**

Highly motivated Full-Stack Developer, with experience in the development and implementation of customized software and web-based applications. Detailed, and highly effective in managing short and long-term projects for existing, new, and emerging technologies, with an emphasis on solving problems that benefit stakeholders.

## **Skills**

JavaScript	React	WordPress	GitHub
Node.js	Redux	Google Analytics	Markdown
HTML	GraphQL	Google Ads	Heroku
CSS	Mongo DB	SEO	Google Firebase

# **Employment History**

Web Developer, Stride Management Corp.

February 2021 - Present

- → Design, develop and deploy responsive web applications to support lottery client projects
- → Optimize applications for speed and efficiency to maximize client's return on investment
- → Offer creative solutions to address the needs of clients
- → Effectively communicate concepts and theories to creative team, select staff, and clients
- → Create secure payment/checkout gateways following regulatory guidelines
- → Perform user flow analysis to improve the conversion rate on lottery client projects
- → Ensure best practices are maintained throughout the project lifecycle

Web Developer/Google Ads Manager, All In One Digital Ltd.

May 2019 - May 2020

- → Designed, developed, and deployed responsive web apps for clients of various industries
- → Designed and implemented website layout strategies to align client goals and values
- → Developed, launched, and monitored PPC Campaigns (Google Ads)
- → Tracked and analyzed the conversion rate and performance of ad campaigns
- → Set specific objectives and reported on ROI and other website analytics and metrics
- → Improved clients search engine optimization enhancing brand awareness
- → Maintained simultaneous project schedules and tasks with strict deadlines

#### **Education**

Web Development Bootcamp, Lighthouse Labs September 2018 - February 2019

## **Selected Projects**

## Alberta Animal Rescue Crew Society

Responsive WordPress website for an Alberta animal shelter, visited by over 80,000 users monthly. Utilizing Toolset, AARCS is able to more efficiently maintain its main source of fundraising, increase animal adoption rate, and further increase its community outreach.

## **Bud Supply Group**

This small town cannabis retailer has been successful at growing to six locations with the assistance of its custom-designed website. With up-to-date inventory, and a design to develop a brand following with MailChimp email capture and OneSignal Notifications.